https://www.bdfcu.com/about/disclosures-privacy/

MENUMENUHomePersonal
SavingsCheckingDebit CardMoney Market Share AccountClub Accounts
Business
Deposit AccountsCash ManagementBusiness LoansRemote Deposit CaptureMerchant ServicesWire Transfer
Loans
Vehicle LoansPersonal LoansLine of CreditHome EquityMortgageShare SecuredCredit CardsStudent LoansSkip-A-Payment
E-Services
Digital Banking & Bill PayE-StatementsK-9 Line Audio TellerDirect DepositMobile BankingApplications
Resources
RatesFinancial PlanningFraud & ID TheftNewslettersHelpful LinksCalculators
Services
ScholarshipsVisa® Gift CardsTruStage InsuranceSafe Deposit BoxWire Transfer
About
HistoryEligibilitySafety and SoundnessDisclosures/PrivacyCareersAccessibilitySite Map
Disclosures/Privacy
Disclosures
Membership and Account Agreement (PDF-new window/tab)
Electronic Funds Transfers Agreement and Disclosure (PDF-new window/tab)
Funds Availability (PDF-new window/tab)
Truth-In-Savings (PDF-new window/tab)
e-Sign (PDF-new window/tab)
Mobile Deposit Capture User Agreement (PDF-new window/tab)
Home Equity Early Disclosure (PDF-new window/tab)
Benefits Plus® (PDF-new window/tab)
Credit Card Disclosure (PDF-new window/tab)
(new window/tab)
Privacy
Bulldog FCU Privacy Policy
FACTS
WHAT DOES BULLDOG FEDERAL CREDIT UNION DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:
Social Security number and account balances
account transactions and credit history
payment history and transaction history
When you are no longer our member, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
How?
All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons Bulldog Federal Credit Union chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information
Does Bulldog Federal Credit Union share?
Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes – such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or to report to credit bureaus
Yes
No
For our marketing purposes – to offer our products and services to you
Yes
No
For joint marketing with other financial companies
Yes
No
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes –
Information about your transactions and experiences
No
We don’t share
Questions?
Call (301) 797-6318 or go to www.bdfcu.com
What we do
How does Bulldog Federal Credit Union protect my personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
How does Bulldog Federal Credit Union collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you
open an account or use your credit or debit card
show your government-issued ID or apply for financing
show us your driver’s license
We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only
sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about your creditworthiness
affiliates from using your information to market to you
sharing for non-affiliates to market to you
State law and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates
Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.
Bulldog Federal Credit Union has no affiliates.
Non-affiliates
Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.
Bulldog Federal Credit Union does not share with our non-affiliates so they can market to you
Joint marketing
A formal agreement between non-affiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
Our joint marketing partners include insurance companies
Download our Privacy Policy (PDF-new window/tab)
(new window/tab)
HOME | CHECKING | BUSINESS | LOANS | RATES | DIGITAL BANKING & BILL PAY | CONTACT US | ACCESSIBILITY | SITE MAP
©
Bulldog Federal Credit Union | Routing #255077516 | Privacy Policy
